So let's just go over a few words that you will need to know in order to really understand the basic
因此，让我们回顾一下您需要知道的几个词，以便真正理解基本知识
ideas behind what we're going to try to accomplish or achieve in this.
我们将在此尝试完成或实现的目标背后的想法。
In this lesson first simplification.
在本课中首先进行简化。
So if you hear somebody say something or you read a book or you watch a movie whenever you talk about
所以如果你听到有人说什么，或者你看书或者看电影，每当你谈论
that thing often you're simplifying what you heard.
那件事通常是在简化你所听到的。
Reducing it so that you can communicate it clearly to others.
减少它，以便您可以清楚地与他人交流。
So simplification means to take something and make it simpler.
所以简化意味着采取一些措施并使其更简单。
This is a simplification if you know something about science that most people don't know and you need
如果您了解大多数人不知道的科学知识并且您需要，这是一种简化
to explain it to someone you have to be able to simplify it or make a simplification in order to explain
向某人解释它，您必须能够简化它或进行简化以便解释
it.
它。
If you read a book and you want to express it you need to be able to simplify maybe some of the ideas
如果你读了一本书并且想要表达它，你需要能够简化一些想法
to explain it to a good friend who might not know much about that topic.
向可能对该主题不太了解的好朋友解释它。
So we're going to try to do this in the second exercise but I just want to make sure you're familiar
所以我们将在第二个练习中尝试这样做，但我只是想确保你熟悉
with the word simplification.
用简化这个词。
It's connected to the word simplify which is a verb simplification is a noun and it comes from also
它连接到简化这个词，它是一个动词，简化是一个名词，它也来自
simple and simple is an adjective of course whoops a D.J. as I usually write it as a D.J..
简单和简单当然是一个形容词，让 D.J.因为我通常把它写成 D.J..
OK.
好的。
Now clarity is also something we have to think about when we're expressing ideas or simplifying something
现在，当我们表达想法或简化某些事情时，清晰度也是我们必须考虑的事情
or explaining something.
或解释某事。
So if you have an idea which is very complicated and you want to communicate it it's very easy to say
因此，如果您有一个非常复杂的想法并且想要传达它，那么说起来很容易
it in a way which makes other people feel more confused because it's a complicated idea or if you're
它以一种让其他人感到更加困惑的方式，因为这是一个复杂的想法，或者如果你是
telling a story it's easy to mix up the details.
讲故事很容易混淆细节。
And when you actually say all of the things you want to say it comes out as all sort of messy and mixed
而当你真正说出你想说的所有事情时，它就会变得混乱而混杂
up.
向上。
So we have to focus on clarity.
所以我们必须专注于清晰度。
Clarity means that when we speak when we write whatever we do.
清晰意味着当我们说话时，我们写下我们所做的一切。
Communication wise we have to try to say things in a way that can not be misunderstood.
在沟通方面，我们必须尝试以一种不会被误解的方式来表达。
The purpose of language is communication and clarity means that things are very clear very easy to understand.
语言的目的是交流，清晰意味着事情非常清楚非常容易理解。
Now the verb for this is clarify.
现在这个动词是澄清的。
So if you have a bunch of people and everybody's arguing and fighting and the reason is because they
所以如果你有一群人，每个人都在争论和打架，原因是因为他们
don't really understand what they're talking about and you really do you could say Excuse me.
真的不明白他们在说什么，你真的明白你可以说对不起。
Let me let me clarify this issue for you.
让我让我为你澄清这个问题。
Let me try to make it simple and clear and easy to understand.
让我试着让它简单、清晰、易于理解。
So we also have to try to bring some clarity to what we're saying.
因此，我们还必须努力使我们所说的内容更加清晰。
Always focus on trying to be simple trying to clarify things good English is not necessarily very complicated
始终专注于尝试简单 尝试澄清事情 好的英语不一定很复杂
often natural English is very simple in fact and good communicators know how to speak clearly.
通常自然的英语实际上非常简单，良好的沟通者知道如何说清楚。
Next is syntax so syntax is an interesting idea.
接下来是语法，所以语法是一个有趣的想法。
We often think of syntax as related to writing but actually syntax is basically the different kinds
我们经常认为语法与写作有关，但实际上语法基本上是不同的种类
of sentences that we choose.
我们选择的句子。
So if you always begin sentences in the same way or you always maintain or keep the same basic sentence
所以如果你总是以同样的方式开始句子，或者你总是保持或保持相同的基本句子
structure and you get into the habit of using maybe it was too much.
结构，你就会养成使用它的习惯，也许它太多了。
That's just an example whatever it is people will begin to sort of lose interest.
这只是一个例子，不管它是什么，人们都会开始失去兴趣。
So it's also important to understand how to say things in different ways use different types of sentence
因此，了解如何使用不同类型的句子以不同方式表达事物也很重要
structures begin sentences in different ways so that when you speak people are interested and they don't
结构以不同的方式开始句子，这样当你说话时人们感兴趣而他们不感兴趣
get bored.
感到厌倦。
It's actually very important to have some variation.
实际上，有一些变化是非常重要的。
And when we say good syntax we're usually looking at writing and saying oh there are some some longer
当我们说好的语法时，我们通常会看着写作并说哦，还有一些更长的时间
sentences some shorter sentences some different types of sentences to say the same type of thing.
句子 一些较短的句子 一些不同类型的句子 说相同类型的事情。
So this shows that you understand English and know how to use it well enough so that when people read
所以这表明你理解英语并且知道如何很好地使用它，这样当人们阅读
what you write or listen to what you say they are fully interested because it's always kind of different
你写什么或听你说什么他们完全感兴趣，因为它总是有点不同
and changing its dynamic.
并改变其动态。
This is a good word to use.
这是一个很好的词。
I like this word dynamic dynamic dynamic.
我喜欢动态动态这个词。
OK.
好的。
The last word is merge.
最后一个词是合并。
So one thing we're going to do today is we're going to take some some words and we're going to try to
所以我们今天要做的一件事是我们要讲一些话，我们要尝试
bring them together into a single sentence we're going to try to merge them into full sentences merge
将它们组合成一个句子 我们将尝试将它们合并成完整的句子 合并
means to bring them together of two big companies come together you merge them.
意味着将它们结合在一起 两家大公司走到一起，您将它们合并。
If there's a big highway and a road that comes up to the highway and you enter onto the highway you
如果有一条大高速公路和一条通往高速公路的道路，而您进入高速公路，您
merge onto the highway.
并入高速公路。
So it basically means to bring together or to become part of something else.
所以它基本上意味着聚集在一起或成为其他事物的一部分。
So we're going to be doing an exercise where we stitch or merge merge different things together into
所以我们要做一个练习，我们缝合或合并将不同的东西合并成
single sentences and you'll see what I mean in a moment.
一个句子，你马上就会明白我的意思。
So I hope these four words are clear and I hope you can keep them in mind.
所以我希望这四个字是清楚的，希望你能牢记在心。